Rebranding a company is one thing.
Proving it drives real results is
another.
>> [music]
>> I'm joined by Jasper CMO L'Oreal Lynch
to talk about how precision targeting on
LinkedIn [music]
helped turn a major brand shift into
measurable impact.
As Jasper worked with LinkedIn to
support its rebrand to an AI-powered
platform, how did you measure success?
>> So, our goal was to turn rebrand
momentum into tangible business growth
that we could actually measure,
>> [music]
>> which means that a lot of the metrics
that we had previously looked at with
respect to marketing campaigns and
particularly brand, you know,
impressions, clicks didn't matter. We
really needed to tie this rebrand to
revenue. We needed to look at pipeline.
>> Why is LinkedIn uniquely positioned to
support a high-consideration B2B rebrand
like Jasper's? [music]
>> There were a couple reasons that we
turned to to LinkedIn when it came time
to launch [music] this rebrand. The
first is that we knew this is where our
audience is. This is where we can find
[music] a highly engaged audience of
exactly the people that we're targeting.
CMOs, enterprise marketing [music]
buyers. And not only can we find them
there, but we know exactly who they are.
But the second reason is a lot of what
came with this rebrand was establishing
[music] thought leadership and
credibility. And just the professional
contacts that LinkedIn is able to offer
allowed us to do that very effectively.
[music]
And what LinkedIn was able to give us
was the knowledge and assurance that our
ads were touching exactly the right
[music] people at exactly the right
time.